Thank you for watching
Commemorating the holding of the Shinzanmono
Captain Sansakamichi's talk
Urgent Live Streaming
Wow!
Yay!
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
Yes, that's right.
The young members of the three slopes of Nogizaka, Hyuga-saka and Sakura-saka...
have gathered together to present a live event
Shinzanmono started on November 3rd!
Wow!
This time, in order to make the performance even more exciting...
We, the captains of the three groups
Let's talk about "Shinzanmono" together!
This is an emergency live broadcast.
What kind of talk is this going to be?
What kind of talk will it be?
I'm looking forward to it!
The hurdle has been raised.
Is this really an emergency live broadcast?
It's really urgent, isn't it?
It was announced yesterday.
I found out yesterday.
Yes, it was.
Maybe a little higher.
A little too much.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Excuse me, sir.
Yes, sir.
So let me introduce myself again.
First of all, let me...
This way?
Excuse me.
I'm Minami Umezawa, captain of Nogizaka46.
Wow.
Hello.
Ume-chan. Ume-chan. And...
I'm Kumi Sasaki, captain of the Hyuhizaka 46. Pleased to meet you.
Kumi, Kumi. Rina Matsuda, captain of Sakura-zaka 46. Pleased to meet you.
Rina Matsuda. Rina Matsuda.
Yes, it's Rina Matsuda.
Is this the first time the three of us have gotten together? Yes, it's the first time.
It's the first time, isn't it?
It's a great opportunity for all of us.
I'm glad we could do it together.
Thank you very much. Each of you has your own color, even in uniform.
Yes, they're all different.
Good evening, everyone. It's already 11:00.
It's almost 4:00. It's almost 4:00.
I'll go with you, please.
I'm glad to hear it.
What's that?
The youngest members of each of the three groups will perform on the same stage for a month.
The first attempt by Sakamichi to have the youngest members of each of the three groups perform live on the same stage for a month.
This is really something.
When I heard about it, I thought it was really cool. When I heard it, I thought it was so wonderful.
I thought so.
There hasn't been a lot of interaction between hillbillies until now.
I thought it would be a great opportunity for a new generation to get to know each other.
Hinata-san and Sakura-san have already started their performance.
It's started. Have you been to see it? You haven't gone yet?
Not yet. I'm watching Sakura-san.
I'm the only one who's still able to go, so I went just yesterday.
I went to see it yesterday, and I was so, so, so moved.
That's right.
I could feel how hard you've been working, and I'm really grateful for that, but I guess tickets are selling really well.
Well...
I heard the battle for the tickets was pretty fierce.
I heard the battle for tickets was fierce, and the capacity was about 900.
Yes, sir.
So thank you very much for all the reports that you couldn't get tickets.
Thank you very much.
For those of you who couldn't make it, I'd like to thank you very much. I'm sure you all know this, but there will be live online streaming of each performance!
There will be live streaming!
Yes!
It's right this way.
Will it come out?
This way.
This way, this way!
We hope many of you will be able to see the performances of Nogizaka Audiences 5th term students, Sakurazaka Uchi 3rd term students, Inada 5th term students, and 4th term students!
Two performances, two performances.
Yes, two performances each.
Two performances each.
And Sakurazaka will be performing the day after tomorrow. And what a surprise, Sakurazaka will be delivered the day after tomorrow, so...
That's right!
I really hope you'll watch it.
It's so good!
I want to see it!
I want to see all of you on all the slopes, too!
I can't wait to go!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'll definitely go on the day I can go.
I want to go!
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it!
And, on the day of the live streaming, there will be a live viewing at 109 Cinemas Premium Shinjuku!
Please check the website for more details.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to seeing you all there!
I think it would be nice to have a total nativity.
Yes, it would be.
I wonder if there will be any eye-openers?
I'm working on it.
It's hard to do, isn't it?
Sounds fun.
Looks like fun.
That's good, too.
Please, please, check it out.
Yes, please check it out.
Yes, I'd like to do Niiza this time, too.
Yes, please. Yes, sir.
For those of you who will be watching the Niiza event at the venue or via streaming.
Yes, sir.
We, the captains of each group, will be responsible for introducing the charms of the members of Niiza-mono.
Yes, I will do my best.
We will do our best.
Each group has its own characteristics, but the young generation is so energetic that we feel like we are being pushed forward again.
That's how I feel.
It makes us want to do our best.
I think so.
It makes us want to do our best, doesn't it?
It's a great feeling.
It's super inspiring.
It's inspiring.
You'll get it.
We're pretty far apart, right?
Yeah, we're pretty far apart.
The youngest is like 16.
I don't know... 8 years apart.
No, that's okay, I'm 13 years younger than you.
Thirteen is so young.
I'm going to introduce you now.
From now on.
They're more mature than you'd expect.
Yes, they are.
That's right.
They are very solid, so I'd like to tell you a lot about them.
So, in this Live Newcomer, we would like to show you what we would like you to see in this fresh group of juniors.
And today, they made this cute card for us, even though we are the predecessors of Emergency. And, you know, today you made this cute card even though it's the front of an emergency!
This is really great!
Isn't the card game cute?
You can see everyone's face on the card along with their picture.
You can summon them as you play the game.
Summoning
Summoning them
Summon and enjoy!
Okay, well, we've got a lot of time, so let's get to it.
No, there's no time.
I don't have time
Not that there is
I'll introduce you right away...
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Well, let me start.
Are you sure?
Well, I'll start with her first.
Summoning
I'm Aya Ogawa, the youngest in Gokisei.
Aya Ogawa!
She's so cute!
It's Aya!
She's a Cancer.
And there...
It's also cute that she's a Cancer.
I'm personally attracted to Aya, too.
That's right.
I have high hopes for her.
And she's 16 now. And he's 16 now.
youngest
I'm the youngest.
She looks like everyone else.
When you meet Aya, you'll instantly fall in love with her.
Wow!
She has a cute face, and she's a tiny little thing, at 5'4".
That's why everyone looks up at her like this.
I can't get enough of it!
I can't get enough of it.
That's right.
We all have a lot of Aya's mothers, but in our group...
But she's not just spoiled. She's a very hardworking, serious girl who tries her best.
That's why everyone loves her so much.
And she looks great at live performances and can play the piano.
She can also play the piano.
And she sings really well, and the other day she was playing the piano and singing...
She sang piano and sang.
And she's also a great hip-hop dancer.
Wow!
That's right.
Part of the unexpected
If she dances hip-hop with this sweet face, I can't help but fall in love with her.
You're right, she's very versatile.
Yes, very versatile.
She can do so many things.
I've fallen in love with her.
Really?
I like her.
Well, I'm glad you liked her the first time. Well, I'm glad you liked her the first time.
Anyway, she has really good visuals and looks great at live performances.
She is small in stature, but she dances big, so I think that makes her very attractive.
I think she's very attractive.
That's Aya, isn't it?
She's cute.
May I introduce our youngest?
Yes, please.
Please.
Summon her.
Summon her!
(clapping)
Rina Watanabe!
Oh!
She's 14 years old!
Wow!
So young!
Fourteen?
That's right, I'm the youngest 14-year-old in Hinatazaka, and I was born in 2009!
2009?
That's a while ago.
Yes, before college.
Rina-chan is called "Mr. Rina" or "Mr. Rina".
Heh...
Mr. Rina is...
Cute Rina.
At 14, you'd think she'd be a bit of a spoiled brat, but she's very firm.
Maybe he's the most solid of the 4th term students.
She's got a look in her eyes like she can see through everything.
Heh. Heh.
And I don't know... this is my subjective opinion, but...
But I was really drawn in by it.
She's very solid, but she's also cute, like a 14-year-old.
She even sneaks out of the dressing room to dance to the latest dance craze.
She even secretly dances to the latest dance craze backstage.
They also have a side to them that makes me feel like they have a side to them.
I'm looking forward to seeing her grow up.
I'm sure you're looking forward to seeing her grow up.
Next, I'd like to introduce you to a girl from Sakurazaka who's been rekindled and burned.
I'd like to introduce you to Matt Nyoyo.
she just turned 17 years old on her birthday... but yes... she's quite a re-burner... but she's quiet...
She's got a cool voice, but she's also got a really nice voice.
Her voice is low and calm, like a matte matte matte matte matte matte voice.
I was a little surprised that she didn't look like she's a little older than me.
I'm from Fukuoka and I'm seven. That's just the way I look.
I'm a big fan of Yui Kobayashi.
I love her so much.
I love her so much that even if I just make eye contact with her, I can't help but feel like I'm a fan.
You know...
I love you so much!
And I can make my own videos.
She makes a face with curly cheeks like she wrote with a name pen, and imitates a newscaster.
I was told that.
Iti I thought it was just a "Gamark" deny, but he seems to like doing funny things like that, and it's pretty funny.
I'm not sure if it's a regret or not, but he likes to do that kind of funny stuff.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm sure it's a good idea.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to make it work for you. answers such as nucaeitoha. Francis and Erica Mtakaeishu-san.
hadi and Liming Ohu eight days away from the King. hadi and Liming Ohu eight days away from the King.
They have such beautiful names, and they're so cute, and they're so energetic.
I can always hear them laughing, or they're always laughing, even when I'm not trying to get them to laugh.
They laugh at me even when I'm not trying to get them to laugh at me.
I'm 17, so I'm a bit of a rock star.
I'm 17, so I've got, like, seven locks, but I've got great fashion sense, and I'm always stylish.
I see it, I see it, I see it... and I love my family.
I'm also really good at paper cutting.
She's really energetic, and she brightens everyone's day.
I'm sure it's also an "ab" type that there are two of you.
I was surprised to see that you are both 66 centimeters tall.
I was surprised to see you both at 66 cm.
Next ire' 63cm
Next, I'm 63 cm.
The performance members are very powerful.
Aishi... can we start with Hyuga-saka?
Rohjon is a member of this group, he's 18 years old and he's an old man!
He's 18 years old, 165 centimeters tall.
Rio-chan is a cheerleader and has danced at the Koshien Stadium.
Wow!
Her smile is so bright and shiny that I want to see her smiling face, and during live performances, I can't help but notice her smile.
I want to be cheered on by Rio, since she used to cheerlead, and she is so sharp.
You have a cute smile, don't you?
Yes, she has a very cute smile. But she is a bit like a cheerleader, you know? But she is a cheerleader, so she is a little bit timid.
She would come to me and ask for my advice. She would come to me for advice, and she had a side of her that was very typical of an 18-year-old,
It made me want to protect her. The cap is nice. The cap is nice. They are such members.
He is one of the members who will really catch my attention at the live performance. I'm looking forward to it.
I think so. It's remarkable. Please pay attention.
And now 15 minutes have passed, and the total number of visitors is over 60,000. Wow!
I don't know what to do. I'm getting nervous. Hey, what should I do? I'm getting nervous.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very much.
I'll introduce more from here. We have a long performance,
I would like to introduce this girl from Nogizaka. Jean! This is Iroha Okuda.
I'm Iroha.
Iroha really shines at live performances,
She sings with a clear and beautiful voice that really draws you in, and she can also play the guitar,
She can also play the guitar, so she can sing by herself on stage,
She is also a very good dancer, and although she is slender and delicate, she is very cool when she performs.
She is both cool and cute.
She has a really good personality.
I instantly felt that she must have come from a good upbringing.
She also has a great posture, which really catches the eye, and I personally love Iroha's ponytail,
I think her ponytail is one of the highlights of the show.
I think they will probably do it in a park somewhere,
So that's my guess.
But anyway, she also has a strong respect for her seniors and is a good girl, so she looks good at live performances,
I think she is a balancer for everyone, or a person who soothes their discomfort.
Isn't she very stylish?
She is very good looking.
Yes, she is.
She can wear anything.
I was surprised when I met her the other day.
She has a long neck and is very cute.
Yes, he is.
I also really like her singing voice.
She has a really cute singing voice.
She has a really nice voice.
Please pay attention to Iroha, too.
I hope you will pay attention to Iroha, too. Attention.
Then, then, Sakura-zaka.
May I?
Please do.
Speaking of dancing, I'd like to introduce Murayuchan.
She's cute.
Murayuchan.
Murayuchan is also really good at dancing, and has been since the beginning,
During the training camp for 3rd term students, "Bang" was the assigned song,
Bang" is one of the most intense songs in Sakurazaka.
It's a very intense song among Sakurazaka's songs. It's fast and intense, and a little bit difficult,
I had some troubles because of my dance background,
But I overcame those problems, and now I am still very good at the sharpness and sharpness that I put in some parts of my dance,
Also, I personally find your hair beautiful.
I was really impressed with his hair. I was able to touch it and it was really smooth, even though it was long,
He handles his hair very well, so it is very powerful during his performances.
But even though he looks cool, he usually looks a bit fluffy.
Wow.
His face looks a bit like a rabbit, doesn't it?
Yes, indeed.
He always comes to look at me in the morning and says, "Good morning!
So cute.
He always greets me with a smile, which is really soothing.
But when it comes to dancing and performing, he's really cool.
I'm going to be Yuu Murai, a member of the group.
I am Yuu Murai, a member of the group. Please give my best regards to her.
Yu-chan.
Oh, sorry.
I'm fine. Did the rabbit fly away a little?
I've been pinching myself. I'm all pinned up.
Then, may I continue with Minato-zaka?
Yes. This is our member. Here we go. Tamaki Ishizuka.
Tama-chan.
Tama-chan is a little bit small (153 cm in height), but she's not too tall,
But she's not small at all.
But she is very powerful.
But everything is powerful.
She is also powerful in her personal life.
Even her personal life.
I'm curious.
I don't have any specific powerful episodes,
No?
But you are always so energetic, and you are really like a beacon of energy for the 4th term students,
When Tama-chan is energetic, we are also energized, and she cheers us all up,
Tama-chan used to be a cheerleader, too.
That is why she is such a dynamic dancer, always smiling, and she cheers us up,
Also, my personal favorite point of Tama-chan is her nose.
Her nose is tall, sleek, and beautiful.
Her profile is so beautiful. When she performs live, there are many moments when we see her in profile.
I would like you to look at her profile.
I would pay attention to it.
I think so.
You are very close to her.
Tama is a really hardworking person who is always trying her best to do everything in a positive way,
I would like you to see her energy.
Please take a look.
Please watch her.
Please pay attention to her.
I want you to pay attention to Tama-chan. Attention.
Okay, then, let me introduce my next one, Riding Slope.
This girl also has a very distinctive dance style.
Okamoto Hina-chan.
Ah, Hina-chan.
Hina has experience in ballet, and she's really good at it.
She's amazing.
I saw her.
She showed us her ballet performance at various events, such as a show-and-tell event, and she has a very soft and flexible body,
One of our songs is called "Sing Out," and the choreography for it is rather graceful, and when I was the center of the song, I saw how beautifully she was growing,
I am very good at that kind of suppleness, and also, I personally think that blue light suits me well. I also have a personal affinity for blue light.
You know what I mean? I like it when the light hits me in the eyes, which is kind of cool, and I like that too,
I like it when the light hits me. She laughs a lot. When Hina is laughing, I feel at ease, and the atmosphere among the members improves,
She is a very charming girl, and she brightens up the atmosphere of the group,
She is a very charming girl, and she brightens up the atmosphere of everyone,
I think the gap between Hina and her live performances is also something to watch out for.
Hina-chan.
I'm looking forward to seeing you.
Next, Sakura, may I have a dance member?
Summon!
I'm Shizuki Yamashita.
Shizuki-chan.
We have the same birthday!
Really?
Surprise!
January 22nd. I didn't expect it to be the same as Kumi's.
We were the same. I'm sorry. I interrupted your instructions.
We were together. Shizuki had been dancing for a long time, and she was very quick to take the turn of the assigned song and make it her own since she joined the group,
I am fronting a song called "Dwarfs in Rest" released by Sakurazaka, and it appears in the song...Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. By all means.
It's...it's some kind of dayflower, isn't it? Something with a hand...
I saw it! You're so good!
This is very good!
Yes, it's been talked about because it's so fast, and it's our newest single, so when we perform this song, I'd like you to pay attention to it,
Also, I am the center of a 3rd term student's song called "Violence of Silence" and I really like this song,
I love this song so much.
I love this song, too, and I think the power of her dance and the way she conveys the song with her facial expression or power of expression are also amazing,
I think their expressions and expressive power to convey the song are also amazing. If you are interested in this band, please check out the song "Violence of Silence".
I love it. I listen to it every day.
Really?
I listen to it every day.
I'm so happy.
I also really like the music video.
Oh, yeah, I'm happy.
The music video is great.
Wow, it's great.
It's cool.
I want you to listen to it.
It's really good.
Please do.
Well, I guess there are some good dancers in this group...
Yes, they are. There are a lot of good dancers in this group.
Yes, it's a live performance.
Yes, we'll have to pay attention to them...
Yes, yes.
I'd like you to follow them...
I'd like to have them.
Yes.
Please do. Please do so.
Yes, please.
Yes.
Yes, I would like to thank you for your comments on this issue.
Thank you for your comments this time.
Yes.
You have received a lot of comments.
I'm getting a lot of comments.
I'm glad.
Indeed.
I didn't see them at all.
I didn't see it at all.
Thank you very much.
A lot.
Wow, oh.
Oh, thank you very much.
Ume-chan is here, too, saying that she listens to you every day.
That's right.
You listen to it?
She says she listens to it.
That's right.
Yes, everyone is...Yeah, guys...
Oh, I'm getting extremely athletic.
Yeah.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I couldn't imagine such a thing... a standing long pole...
I couldn't jump.
I've never done it before... and I'm a very good dancer.
I'm a good dancer even if I'm not a great dancer.
I'm sure the three of us are going to have a lot to talk about, but I'm still a little nervous.
I'm not very good at presentations, so I'm trying really hard to do my best, but I'm not sure if I can do it well.
charm, you might actually be able to do it!
I'm going to ask you to start with Sakura.
This is the next one...
She's very pretty, very playful, very tall, and at 168 centimeters, she's one of the tallest girls in the group.
She's 168 centimeters tall. She's one of the tallest girls in the group.
I've never met her before.
I had never met her before and she was introduced to me on a private video.
I liked the color black, but I can't wear black, so please show me your heads...
Give it to me.
I thought everyone wanted to see red, but this girl is also really good at dancing.
She's a very good dancer, and she's tall, so she can really bring out her power, but is she a little strange like that?
I thought she might be a little strange or cool, but she talked to me very enthusiastically.
I kept saying, "Yes, and this, and that," and he made me feel really comfortable talking to him.
They asked me questions and talked to me about various things, and there was a surprisingly friendly side to them.
She's not just friendly with me, but also with the other senior members. She looks cool, but she's surprisingly friendly and sweet.
She's cute, isn't she?
She's cute.
She's cute. negative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
I'm good at dancing, too.
I am also a good dancer, of course, but I think I have the power to draw people to me.
I personally think that she has the power to reach out to people through her power of expression, so please pay attention to her performance.
I can't do the above... Okay, I'll leave it at that.
This is
This is REVE.
I'm going to delete all the other files...
Ao
Oh!
I'm Nana Kaneko
Konishi Konishi
It's like a voice
Unusual
He's a good boy.
for a moment
I'm happy
or внут É
is amazing
O Expang
Hold me.
what a beautiful and
Cute.
I've seen her many times with clear eyes and nose.
Her smile is cute, but especially when she sings a cool song, she seems to have a very mature look to her.
She has a cute smile, but especially when she plays a cool song, she has a very mature face, even though she's only 19 years old.
I have long black hair that's really straight and silky, and I think she's really beautiful.
I thought she was going to pop out at some point, but she's a real Kansai girl.
She even made a dig at me in her Kansai dialect, which was quite amusing. He would even go into it in his Kansai dialect, which was quite funny.
I love it.
I'm sure he also makes little comments on mc and other places, but I haven't been able to go see him yet, so I can't say for sure.
He's fashionable and likes to dress stylishly and wears unique clothes that suit him.
I like to wear fashionable clothes.
And he sometimes wears his bangs parted at live shows.
I remember that I like this one the best. I've seen it again, so it's current.
I personally like it. I think it's nice.
I'm sure we'll be able to see it on some of the days we'll have it open for distribution.
I'm not a McCool type, but I'm this girl Ah, Nakanishi.
She's a good singer.
She's really good at singing and she can sing Nogizaka's songs and make them her own
Also, when everyone sings together, I think it's Aru's voice, she's so good at making it her own.
And she has her own world view so much that when she stands in the center of the stage, the atmosphere of the concert space changes at once.
She has the power to control the atmosphere of the live space, and she can instantly create her own atmosphere just by being there.
I always thought she was really cool.
But she's also surprisingly petite.
But I also think he's cool looking, and he has a great sense of words, and he chooses his words beautifully.
I have such a cool image, but I'm also a bit of a klutz.
She's not very athletic either.
And her mother is very cute... and she likes barbecued meat.
She's also very skilled and has a cool image, but she also seems to be a bit of a ditzy kid.
She also has a lot of cute parts like a meat lover.
Anyway, I'm sure you'll be able to see the moment when she really makes the space her own at her live performances, which I think you'll see in the live performances of Nogizaka's second term students, so I'd like you to pay attention to that.
Ar-no Ar-no Ar-no!
Okay, so we'll start with Sakurazaka from the end of this month.
If you know Yuzuki Nakajima's character, you might think she's cool.
She looks mature and she's a Hakata beauty from Fukuoka, but she's a girl who works hard at variety shows.
I don't know what it is... She's not really weird, but she's kind of...
She's not strange, but she's funny and interesting. I don't know how to put it into words, she's not a wonder kid, but she's funny, funny, funny.
She's funny and funny, and now she's a regular in the season that Rabbit needs her more.
She's doing a great job there, too, but she's also one of our third-term students.
I see her as a great helper, or rather, as a person who is in charge of making sure things are done right.
She tries her best in variety shows and is a bit funny, but the parts where she is firm are very firm.
And then there's the other thing... what did you want to say?
But if there's a scene, Nakajima's usually in charge.
I've been doing a lot of mc work since I started here, and Akashima has been doing the same thing since the beginning.
Akashima has been like that since the beginning, consulting with me about mc and so on, and he's been working really hard.
She didn't have a mv, but she was the center of a recent song, and she performed a very cute idol song.
Yuzuki is very energetic and bright, and her performance is very cute and cheerful, and I think she can give energy to everyone.
I hope you will pay attention to her.
Okay, then, let's continue with the mc, mc, mc, and mc.
I'm Mizuki Hiraoka and this is Mi-chan and Mi-chan is her avatar.
She's the oldest of the fourth graders, so she's kind of like an older sister to the Ones.
Micchan's pretty solid, but she's also kind of funny.
She's not a natural, but she has a funny side.
Recently I noticed that his posture is very good, which is not a bad thing, but he has a funny reaction to it.
I have a funny reaction to it, and it's a little bit of a turn-on for me, so there's that funny side to me, and I get a lot of flack from people.
But I also think that she is the big sister who watches over everyone and organizes the 4th term students.
I think she's the big sister who organizes the 4th term students.
Michi is very protective of me.
She's really supportive of me.
That's right... that's why I'm doing it too.
I heard that Hiraoka also has a great sense of words and uses phrases like that.
He also likes to read books like novels, and he writes a blog like a novel, and I'm sure mc has a glimpse of a novel.
I sometimes think that she uses wonderful words and phrases, so please pay attention to her!
I'll be watching you because you dance so happily and joyfully.
I'll have a jellyfish, and I'll have a mc-like heart.
Satsuki Sugawara! Satsuki Sugawara.
Satsuki is also known as Masayoshi, a nickname given to her by Bananaman's Shodara.
Satsuki also plays the center role in Gokisei's songs.
SallyGenack, have you ever seen her before? She looks surprisingly cool, though she looks empty in the picture.
I'm not sure if it's true, but it looks cooler than it is.
I'm a senior who is very charming and talks to me a lot, so when I'm turning mc's, I'm very good at it.
He can do anything, he's really good at everything, he can do cute, cool, and crazy.
Yes, I'm fun, so even though I'm in my fifth year, when I go to CrossFit, they say Satsuki is all-rounded, but I'm a bit of a favorite, so the staff says I can do cute, cool, and even crazy.
So even though I'm a 5th year student, I'm sure Satsuki can handle it.
She makes me feel secure that Satsuki will be fine if I hit and shake her.
She's very friendly and cute.
She's slender and has a great style.
She can wear any Nogizaka outfit.
So I don't know which outfit she will wear this time.
I don't know which costume she will wear this time, but I think it will be a highlight for the audience to see her in all the Nogizaka costumes.
I also like the gap between her performance and speech, so I think it will be interesting to see.
Yes, Shokichi!
Shokichi.
Go for it!
It's been almost 40 minutes.
Oh my, 74,000 viewers!
That's great!
Are we talking too much?
But we have so much to say.
We don't have enough.
Yes, we do.
We're going over the date.
That's true.
We're going over.
We have to keep going. We have to keep going.
Let's keep moving.
There's more where that came from.
I'll start from the Hyugaizaka slope.
Please do!
Come on, come on!
That's it!
I'm Sumire Miyaji.
Sumire-chan!
Sumire.
Sumi Legend!
Sumi Legend.
I have a nickname.
Cool.
It's a cool nickname.
Sumi Legend is a nickname that Tamaki Ishizuka gave me.
She is quite lovely and pretty.
She's very pretty and pretty.
Onion.
Boo-boo is good. Please read it.
I'm Regie Regie Kasumi... but she has a really small face.
I'm an elf with a really nice face, and I've been playing baton for a long time, so I've got a little bit of a ballet thing going on.
She's got a little bit of a ballet look to her, so she's got a great style, and when she's on stage she's a real eye-catcher.
Yes, she has a very thin and stylish body, but she dances dynamically, so she's kind of a legend.
I think "Leger is amazing" because he dances so dynamically.
I thought he's very fluffy.
And then there's that guy... who seems to be so fluffy, but he's so loud... when he's doing his mc.
at the time of mc.
I want to see how cute they are, and I want to get to know them...
There's a lot of noise here, you know... This place is full of J's!
If you can see it, you can see it.
When I saw that you put Kotani in the picture, I thought it was really wonderful, and I felt that you were supporting it behind the scenes.
I feel like he's supporting the artist behind the scenes.
Why is it that he has such a powerful eye and he finds the camera so quickly?
She's so quick to find the camera, even when she's being photographed like this.
She's an idol in a dress.
I can't help but think, "Oh, she's so cute!
Sumi-chan, please take care of her.
I'm going to this school because I'm a bit cute and I'm going to Miku Ichinose's school because I'm a bit cute and I'm a bit cute and I'm a bit cute and I'm a bit cute
I have a nickname for her, "Kyunkyun", but she has a special move, "Mi-kyun".
I'm going to do the "Mee-kyun-kyun" move.
I think if they do that, everyone will fall in love with them.
But when she gets nervous, she laughs.
She smiles all the time, and she says that she feels relieved and that her smile has become frozen.
She never slows down her pace, so she's really good at mc as well, and she soothes everyone's atmosphere.
And he talks slowly and leisurely, so I feel calm too.
He speaks slowly and slowly, so it makes me calm down, too.
She makes me feel at ease, and she's a serious and hardworking person, and she's like a big sister to the students. She brings out the best in everyone, so I guess she's like a mother to us all.
She also likes Arya, whom I love, very much, and they have a good relationship, and I hope you'll pay attention to their interaction at the live performance.
Anyway, I'm sure they can make Mi-kyawaii cute, so please pay attention when they play those songs.
Please pay attention to them when they play those songs.
So next is Sakura Mochi, a cute girl of course, since she's Sakura
Of course she's Sakura, so of course she's cute...
She's a little petite girl, but she's 151 centimeters tall, which is one of the tallest in the group.
She's also a very good dancer.
I was the center of the song, and I was able to express powerful dance moves with my small body.
You dance well, but you also sing very well.
She has a very nice singing voice, and her way of saying things is a little characteristic, and I'm sorry if you don't like it, but she has a way of saying things that sounds a little bit clumsy.
I love radio so much that I can forget about it even if I love it personally. The radio is amazing I love it so much I could love it personally and forget about it.
I love it, I love it, I love it.
There it is!
I can love and forget the violence of silence.
I didn't listen to Baichi.
I haven't listened to Vice.
You haven't heard the great bachi.
Right there.
That's great!
It's not that I think she has a bad tongue or anything, it's just that Airi has a distinctive singing voice, and I personally think it's really great.
She can also play the guitar, so she can sing a little bit, and she's very versatile and can peel eggs out of their shells in a spiral.
Oh, I think I've seen her before.
Ah, I think I've seen something like that before.
Eggs are peeled in this way.
I can peel an egg in this way, and since I love Mr. Joyman, I can also peel an egg while saying, "I love that one!
I also love to peel eggs in this way, and I also love Mr. Joyman, so I can peel eggs while saying "Nanah Nanah".
I'm Airi Taniguchi.
Next...
Okay.
Yes, yes.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Yes. Yes. Yes, sir.
Yes ale
Silk
Re
ale
is
il
kits
wheat
anger
defeat
I know you have "Sakura Kawasaki Chan-nya sakutan sakutan sakutan", I know that.
I know it's not there yet, but it's already become a part of my life.I was already familiar with her, but I didn't start talking to her until I saw Sakutan wrinkling her wrinkles.
I don't know... in a good way... she's 20 years old, but she looks so young... but when you talk to her, she seems mature...
She's so cute. If she looks at you in the eyes, you'll be taken by her.
The other day, the members and I were talking about how much we want to be shortstops.
The members adore her. She's got that crying face.
Girls like her face and guys will be attracted to her too.
And she used to be a figure skater.
She used to be a figure skater.
That's why her dancing is so graceful.
She has a strong core.
His turns are beautiful.
I think that's what makes her attractive.
Also, when she gets nervous, she sometimes makes a straight face.
It's easy to see and it's so cute.
But when I relax and smile, I have a big smile.
That's really cute.
And when he speaks during MC, he has a nasal voice.
Sakutan is something like Gomezao, right?
He'd say, "Sakutan is Mr. Gomezao, isn't it?
That's also very cute.
That's why I'm paying attention to him.
And his hair is really long.
Her hair is beautiful.
It's so beautiful.
It's really long and beautiful.
I think the way she uses her hair when she turns is also noteworthy.
Sakutan
I wonder if she'll do wrinkles, wrinkles, wrinkles.
I wonder if she's going to do it.
Next time, we'll do cherry blossoms. The next one is still in Sakura.
I have a member who's cute as a baby.
Morikawa-chan.
I'm Ennriko.
Ennriko.
Ennriko, you really look like a baby.
It makes me want to congratulate her.
I think all the members are like that, and so are the fans.
She has a baby-like face.
But she also has a baby-like atmosphere.
But deep down inside of her, she has a heart that hates to lose.
Passionate
Hot!
So passionate.
I just don't want to lose.
For example, in the physical fitness test...
You know that bridge?
How far can you get with that?
I'm so disappointed to lose.
I'm so frustrated that I'm losing.
Almost zero!
I'm going to challenge until it's almost zero.
He's so determined to win.
She's so adorable in a way.
She hates to lose.
That's why she's a hard worker and can play the drums and clarinet so well.
He's so cool when he plays the drums.
It's like a baby playing drums.
A baby playing drums.
It's really cool. That's really cool.
I've been practicing difficult drums like this.
He's practicing and practicing and practicing and practicing.
In his first personal PV, he shows those drums.
I think you can see Enriko's cool drumming in the video.
I think it's a good idea to show off your ability to play an instrument like that.
I hope you'll watch the video and check out that part of her performance.
This is Riko with her baby!
Cute baby, cute baby, cute baby!
Next, I have another baby-like girl.
This is Nao Tomisato.
You can tell by her face, can't you?
She's a baby, but she's really a baby.
She's a baby, but she's very tall for a baby.
She's very stylish and has a nice gap between the two.
And she's a good-natured person, in the best sense of the word.
She makes a lot of things happen.
jakby, even though I was the one who came up with the idea...
Even if she is the first one, she spoils the baby....
I think they have become so unique, and in no time at all, they are being expressed.
It is expressed in a way that is not small.
I think a lot of fans do this too.
I think a lot of fans do it too.
I often say, "Let's go, everyone!
His voice is really good!
I was so surprised when I heard her voice.
I was like, "This girl can do this kind of thing.
Her voice is surprisingly fluffy, but she also has a thick voice.
But she also has a beautiful voice like a voice actress.
So anyway, she has a good voice. So anyway, he has a good voice.
She is also the center of the latest song of the 5th term students.
She was also selected for the next single for the first time.
She's working really hard and getting better and better.
I'd like you to pay attention to her growth as well.
I'm Naonao.
Nao Nao
Nao Nao looks great live!
This is not my baby.
I'd like to introduce you to the members here.
Hey!
Oh, I made a mistake!
Kirarin!
Kirarin, this is the second time for sure!
Kirarin-chan, you've got T-cells!
Kirarin!
She's close to the baby.
I'm Haruka Yamashita.
This is Haruka Yamashita.
Haruka!
Her name is Haruharu.
Haruharu is 20 years old, second from the top in the 4th term.
She's like a big sister to me and Micchan.
She's a natural!
She's a natural, but she's got a lot of flaws.
I don't know how to say it.
She doesn't know the meaning of words, but she uses difficult ones.
That's what they mean.
He's a little bit cute. He's kind of a cute guy.
That's why he thinks he's talking.
He thinks he's using the right words.
He's got a cute smile, even though he's got a "haha" moment.
She has a friendly smile that makes me go "haruharu" easily.
Even if I'm wrong, it's okay.
She has that kind of power.
It really brings peace to everyone.
If Haruharu is smiling, then everyone will be at peace.
But she also has a funny side.
But she also has a funny side, and I'm sure she has a lot of explosive power when she MC's.
There is a third term member named Yamaguchi.
There is a third term member named Haruo Yamaguchi.
He says that he wants to be in Yamaguchi's mouth.
He said something like, "I want to be in the mouth of Mr. Yamaguchi.
I'm going to tear it off.
It's strange.
That's strange.
But he's got a lot of passion inside him.
They'd say, "I'm going to do my best," or, "Seeing you guys on stage made me want to work even harder.
They even told me directly.
They respect me so much, but they also have a mysterious side to them.
I can't take my eyes off them.
Their smiles make me happy.
That's the kind of member I like.
Also, he has a great style.
Hee...
Yes, really.
She looks great in all her outfits, and her face is so small. She has a small face and looks great in all kinds of hairstyles, so please pay attention to her at the show!
Please look out for them at the live! I look forward to working with you.
This is Nagisa Kojima, a little girl from Sakurazaka who also has some hot things at home and some solid parts, but she's also a little bit of a...
I'm Nagisa Kojima, and this is the first time I've seen a tree like this.
I've never met her before, but I've seen her videos on Sakurazaka's channel during the training camp, and I thought that she's a bit of a jerk.
I thought about how I was leading the discussion at the meeting, or how I was leading the group at the dance.
She is the kind of girl who actively says, "I'm going to pull everyone together," or "I'm going to do something about this," and I think it's very reassuring to have someone like that to pull you along.
She is also good at studying.
She's also a very good student, and she's so smart that she got 22 A's on the Sakurazaka test.
She can also play the piano.
He can play the opening part of a live concert.
I can play the piano in such a cool way that the live performance starts from the opening part.
I can play the piano, and I can do sports too.
She's also the center of the latest song "Morinin" by the 3rd term students.
She is also the center of the latest song called "Morinin" which is a song for the 3rd term members.
I'm not sure if it's because I'm a member of the first or second term, but it's a song that really sticks with me, especially when I hear it from the perspective of a member of the first or second term.
The dance is also expressed by everyone in the song, so I would like you to pay attention to the guardians who are playing the center and watch the music video.
Oh, she also likes video games and anime.
It's a little personal.
I haven't had a chance to talk with him yet, so I'm sorry about the game.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to make it sound like a game, but that's one of the things I'd like you to pay attention to.
Now let's continue with the members who can do anything, Kaho Fujishima
I'm Kaho, Kaho Rin Kaho Rin Kaho Rin Kaho Rin Kaho Rin
Gahorin Gahorin Gahorin Gahorin
Gahorin Gahorin Gahorin
Kahorin is from Hokkaido, and she seems to have grown up in a very spacious and vast land. She's very laid back and fluffy, loves to sleep, and loves sheep.
He loves to sleep and he loves sheep, but he's surprisingly observant of his surroundings.
He's very fluffy, but he's got a lot of guts.
He is very good at everything he does. I'm pretty good at everything.
He's pretty reckless.
Kahorin, she's always telling me what to do, and she's always doing it.
She's so nice and cute... she's the one who stands in the middle of the 4th graders and brings us all together.
She has a laid-back attitude that envelops everyone, and I think she's a key member of the group.
She sang the center of a 4th term member's song called "Somatronic Monster" and it was really exciting at the live.
It's my favorite song because it's got a lot of spice to it, and I think you can hear Hori's voice in many different songs at live performances, so please pay attention to Ahorin.
I'm sure you'll be able to hear her singing a variety of songs at the concert, so please pay attention to her!
I've already got a date!
I'm glad you're late... and I'm glad we've got the date together.
I'll talk a lot more.
I'm not sure what to say, but I'm sure you'll find it interesting.
I'm not saying that you can't go to Mao's if you want to be healed... but if you want to be healed, you can't go to Mao's...
She's got beautiful teeth and she's cute... and she's got a great style.
And her face is so tiny.
It's double the style.
She's tall and cool, but I feel like I want to protect her.
He often makes a troubled face, and when I think he's probably in trouble, I want to approach him.
And Mao is a very kind-hearted girl, so when she sees her classmates are crying, she makes a face like this.
When she cries or something, she rushes to the market and she has a kindness that embraces everyone.
She has the ability to apply her kindness and healing power to everyone.
She has a very beautiful singing voice, a bit husky or something, and she has a unique voice.
It's a little bit...
I think Mao's good point is that she is cute but when she sings, she sounds strong or you can see her strength.
I'm sure she'll show us many performances like that at the live.
Thank you very much.
I was surprised to hear that too...
She's Shogenji's cousin.
She's Iioki's cousin, and they look alike, don't they?
She's a high school student. He looks like a boy.
He plays the flute and looks like a flute player.
He's serious and can study hard. He's serious, but he loves anime.
That's right.
He can't stop talking about anything he likes. He's a little boyish like that.
When he starts to perform, he becomes a resident of the song or the main character of the song, and I've never seen his face like this during a performance.
The way Yohkoh was so absorbed in the song that I had never seen such a face before was very attractive, and when he appeared on the monitor, I felt as if my heart was grabbed by him.
And also, they love to joke around and make people laugh, so they are very positive about that as well.
They're also very positive about that kind of thing.
Yes, her trademark is her outer wings. She says so, so I'm sure she looks great in them.
I'm sure that's another point of interest.
Please take a look at the side of the testimonial site.
Let me start with Sayarasaka.
Rika, Ishimori and him!
Rika is the oldest member of the 23rd term, but her voice is so soft and fluffy.
She has a really cute voice, and I personally like her singing voice.
She sings well, and I think she can add a lot of nuance to her voice.
I think I can add nuance to my voice, and I think about how I want to sing it, and I think she has a great voice.
I think I have a really good voice, and I'm really good at cooking, and I'm good at cooking omelettes.
He made an omelette on the show and it was really delicious.
He's also very dexterous, and I get the impression that he's kind of fluffy.
When the music for the van competition was selected, the center was decided by lot drawing.
When we performed the song at various live performances, there was a line that said, "What time is it?
But he said it in his own way.
The way he said that line was so powerful, I could see the science that I usually know, but not the science I usually know.
So when it comes to that kind of performance, you get to see a completely different side of him, but it's also very healing.
The oldest member of the group, Ishimori Rika, is a very cute girl who also gives us a healing experience.
There's also a girl who can heal you right now... and she's so kind and soothing... and that's Sheen.
Next, from Nogizaka, we have a girl who's a little bit more solid.
Nagi Nagi was the center of the title song of this year's Nogizaka. Naginagi was the center of the title song of this year's Nogizaka group, and yes, I don't know what to say about her, but she's been very strong since she came into the group.
She sings and dances well, and she's also very good at showing herself at live performances.
Anyway, her eyes are very important, and she probably studies even the movement of her eyes when she performs live.
I think even the way her eyes move when she performs live is something she's been studying.
I can't believe she's 18, she seems so calm. She's very mature, but I think she's got a hint of sass.
But I also think she's got a bit of a sassiness to her.
I wonder if anyone can understand that... and I think that's part of what makes her so idol-like.
Also, since I am the eldest daughter, I play the role of a mother.
She takes good care of me, and I think that's one of the things that makes her the center of the group.
And her drawings are really good.
I've heard that he's really good at drawing, not just good, but he's a professional.
She has a lot of charm and specialties.
I don't know, there was no monitor at the live performance, so I hope you will pay attention to her beautiful dance performance as a whole.
Naginagi, you're so cute!
She's a little...
You're good!
And now for another one, Teresa Ikeda, Teresa Ikeda, Teresa Teresa-chan, popping with her telepnece!
As you all know, Teresa is a student at the University of the Arts, and she's also active, and I'm sure it's really hard to balance both, isn't it?
She's also very busy with her school life, and she's doing her best while juggling high school and school.
She has a great artistic talent, a very good choice of words, and she's very smart, so she's a little strange, but she's like a big sister to me.
Theresa's lack of depth is a little confusing, and I think that's what makes her so beautiful.
Also, she has a beautiful face.
She has a beautiful face.
I feel like I'm going to be sucked in when I look into her eyes.
Her eyes are big, too.
I hope you can see her at the live performance because she is very close to the audience.
Also, she has always loved Nogizaka and has a strong Nogizaka-esque image.
Also, I'm playing the center of one of my favorite songs, "Kokoro no Nai Koto", and I don't know if I'm going to do it.
I don't know if he'll play it or not, but it's my favorite song and I told him I like it.
I don't know if he'll play it, but it's my favorite song, and I even told him I liked it. I would like you to pay attention to the live performance.
Telepan
Oh, yeah, Nogizaka is over!
It all happened so fast!
It all happened so fast.
I hope everyone got the message.
I think they got the message.
They got the message.
These girls, please.
They're so cute.
Please, please, please.
Next, we'll do Sakurazaka for the last time.
Sakurazaka, but it's a little bit...
Division Ryodo...
Ryodo...
There are members who are both ways.
Tell me about it!
I'm Reina Kozakura.
Sakura's really smart, too.
I know...
But I have an image of her that way.
She's the smartest member of Sakurazaka and ranked first in the achievement test.
That's to be expected.
He also went to Keio University!
Wow!
That's amazing!
He's from Keio University, isn't he?
He really worked hard during rehearsals while going to college. I've been working really hard on this rehearsal while going to college.
I probably don't have as much time as I thought I would.
Soon yellow resumes
That's the reason why I have to go out there and get them.
Soon ah that kind of song I think there are a lot of girls
I'm sure there's a lot of girls out there.
I really don't know.
I don't know.
That's great.
You know what?
Collaboration repeated
Oh, yeah.
Hey there
there
Time is
of this place
And the Corollis Codes.
Well.
Revolutionary.
easy to play
I've heard that
I've heard that it's easy to play
I don't know...
Inside
This is
playing with things
moving
And there, too.
Amazing!Wow!
I'm a little bit surprised to see a young lady who can carry on the tradition of our second Yuka Sugai, the former captain of the group.
Now we have a girl who inherits a young lady who reminds me a little of Ms. Sugai, the former captain of the group.
But she's also a little fluffy and elegant.
I thought she was quite a young lady, but she was so geeky.
She was so, so, so gibberish.
I can't get into it.
Yes, when I try to explain something funny, I can't go on.
I couldn't go on, I couldn't laugh and talk about it.
I recently realized that it might be the most surprisingly funny thing I've ever seen.
I think that's a very good, interesting, and cute gap.
Also, he recently started playing golf? I heard he started playing golf.
You've been doing that on YouTube?
Yes, he plays golf as a hobby.
She's also really good at making sweets.
I've eaten some of them.
Florentine? I've also made difficult pastries that look so delicious that they look like they're made in a restaurant.
She is also a good student and works really hard.
I think she can deliver an amazing performance.
I hope you will pay attention to her performance.
This is Reina Odakura.
Now, let's go on to the last member from Hyugaizaka, who is in this Niiza group.
Here she is!
Honoka Hirao
Hana-chan from Fannan.
She has a special move called "Hiraho"!
Yes, she's always doing her special move called "Hiraho".
I'm sure you can see it at the live performance.
Hirao played the center role for the first time in the latest song "Rock Climbing" by the 4th term members.
He has beautiful eyes that seem to draw you in, no matter if he's smiling, playing a cool song, or whatever. He has really beautiful eyes that take you in, no matter what he's doing, whether he's smiling or playing a cool song.
Even when they are smiling or playing a cool song, their eyes are so clear that I feel like I'm laughing out loud.
I thought she was a little soft and fluffy, but then I was surprised.
But I thought he was a little fluffy, but then I realized he had a great sense of humor and used unique words.
He has a good sense of words.
I was given a nickname, too.
It's called "Azabu Juban in the early afternoon.
What? The fence.
For me.
You get out a lot.
You do that a lot.
Mr. Wakabayashi has an addiction to Mr. Kasuga.
I want you to put it on.
I want you to put it on me
Maybe he'll give it to me.
It's funny.
He says he's sorry, but he's doing a great job at variety shows.
He's done a lot of variety shows.
He used to be really good at comedy.
That's great.
It makes me laugh.
She's got that side of her too.
I used to be a little bad at dancing.
I wasn't very good at dancing, but I've been getting really good at it.
She dances perfectly with everyone and is a very hard worker.
But when she's nervous, she stares at one move or the other.
She's also cute and easy to recognize.
I'm sure she also does rock climbing.
I'm sure she also does rock climbing, so please pay attention to her performance at the center.
I'd like you to pay attention to her appearance at the center. I'm looking forward to working with you.
There is another knight of the book, Honoka, and a double Honoka at Hyugaizaka.
The other knight is absent from Niiza this time.
But I'm sure all the four knights are doing their best to make up for him.
I hope you will pay attention to them as well.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
And that's it, I'm done introducing everyone!
I've been talking over the date of the burger.
I know we've been talking about this for more than just a few days now, but I'd like to end on a high note.
I feel like I've learned a lot about the junior members of each other's sound groups, and it's made me want to go and see them.
I also felt like I wanted to go and see them... and not only my own group.
There may be a group that you like, but there's definitely something attractive about their live performances, so I hope you'll see them all.
I want you to see all of them.
So, here are the tickets for Niiza Mono's live streaming.
The second half of the Nogizaka season will be held on November 27th and December 3rd.
Sakurazaka-san's schedule is November 12 and December 2.
If you start tomorrow, it will be November 18 and November 30.
You can look at all the groups and compare them, and also compare the points we have recommended to you.
I hope you could feel the goodness of all of them.
I hope you could feel the goodness of everyone and we had a lot to talk about.
I hope we can talk about that too.
We haven't talked about us at all.
We haven't talked about us at all, but we can't talk about it, so we're going to start.
It's complicated.
Kumi's my senior, but we're almost the same, only a few days apart.
I'm glad to see you, Kumi.
Matsui-chan is my junior.
Not at all, considering she's the same age as our Hinano and third-term students. Not at all. I was just thinking about our Hinano and her being in the same class as the 3rd term students.
That's great! Thank you so much!
If there's anything else, we'll talk about it.
Then, please do. Please do.
It's tough on both of us, but yes.
Everyone's working hard, and so is the group.
We're all growing up so fast.
Misaka doesn't really get to know each other that well.
But I want to make the whole Sakamichi group more exciting.
We're still going strong. We're going to do our best.
I'm looking forward to your support. I hope you'll all do well.
I hope you'll all do your best. We've got a lot of live shows coming up.
So, please come and watch the Niiza Mono streaming.
I hope you all enjoy the live streaming of the Niiza Mono, the live viewing of the Niiza Mono, and the live viewing of the Niiza Mono!
All right, everyone.
See you again!
Good night.
Thank you for staying up late.